http://www.webcontacts.com.au/help#contact-and-hours

Skip to main content
Welcome! WebContacts is now part of Clearly Australia. Same awesome Aussie service, with extra benefits for you!
(Learn more)
WebContacts is now part of Clearly Australia!
Same Aussie service, extra benefits.
(Learn more)
Merry Contacts to all!
SHOP CONTACTS
Time to refill?
Reorder in just 3 clicks
Reorder
Learn More
Time to refill?
Reorder in just 3 clicks (Learn More)
Reorder
Time to refill?
Reorder in just 3 clicks (Learn More)
Reorder
Easy Reorder
Reordering your contacts is easy: Three steps and you're done!
1. Click the "Reorder" button
It may ask you to login if you haven't already.
2. Select your contacts
Click the Reorder button below to add them to your cart.
3. Checkout!
All of your information will be filled in and ready to go.
Reorder now
Australia's #1 OnlineEyewear Store*
Trusted by 5 million customers around the world.
*according to IbisWorld's 2019 Report "Online Eyeglasses and Contact Lens Sales in Australia"
Australia's #1 OnlineEyewear Store*
Trusted by 5 million customers around the world.
*according to IbisWorld's 2019 Report "Online Eyeglasses and Contact Lens Sales in Australia"
Australia's #1 OnlineEyewear Store*
Trusted by 5 million customers around the world.
*according to IbisWorld's 2019 Report "Online Eyeglasses and Contact Lens Sales in Australia"
Shop Contacts
Feel the everclear difference
everclear: 40% cheaper than the leading brand + free shipping on your order.
Feel the everclear difference
everclear: 40% cheaper than the leading brand + free shipping on your order.
Feel the everclear difference
everclear: 40% cheaper than the leading brand + free shipping on your order.
Your Stories
The ordering process was super easy and I received my contacts in great time. Their contacts were much better than the pricier options I have tried before.
Nia
Ridiculously fast shipping and such awesome pricing!
Jess
Ordered my contacts on Wednesday at 6pm and they arrived Friday before 12pm. Shipping is so fast and well packaged, customer service is great and the products haven’t let me down yet!
Justine
Why buy your contacts lenses online from Clearly
We make it easy to order your contacts with a wide selection of lenses, great prices, and free returns. We stock an extensive selection of brand names like Alcon,
Bausch + Lomb,
CooperVision, and Acuvue.
How is Clearly different?
We recognize that no two eyes are the same. You and your eye care professional have a plan for your vision, and we're here to make sure you can find the vision correction you need at a price you'll love so you can enjoy
clear, uncompromised sight.
Which contact lenses do we stock?
Clearly carries everything from single vision, multifocal/bifocal, and toric lenses in daily,
weekly, and monthly variations - plus coloured
contacts for people wanting to change their look in the blink of an eye.
Sign up for news and exclusive offers.
Your e-mail address
Sign Up
You can unsubscribe at any time. Please see our
privacy policy
Sign up successful!
You're good to go! Thank you for joining.
Looks like you’ve already subscribed!
Add us to your favorites so you don’t miss out
The Clearly Difference
Our Story
Our Mission
International Sites
United States
Canada
New Zealand
Healthfunds
Need your eyes checked?
1800 639 478 Clearly Coupon Codes
Eye Health
How to read your prescription
Eye Health FAQ’s Contact Lens Misconceptions Contact lens care
International Sites
United States
Canada
New Zealand
Copyright © 2020 Clearly. All rights reserved.
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Sitemap
New customers get 15% off first order of contacts & free shipping when you sign up for email
You can unsubscribe at any time. Please see our
Privacy Policy
Sign up
Please enter a valid email address.
You can unsubscribe at any time. Please see our
Privacy Policy
New customers get 15% off first order of contacts & free shipping when you sign up for email
Sign up for email to get code
Sign up»
We promise to never share your information.
Privacy Policy
Oz Contacts is now part of Clearly Australia
We're excited to share that Oz Contacts has merged with Clearly Australia, which means you can now shop for the contact lenses you already love, with plenty of new benefits.
Same awesome Aussie service - and so much more
Fast and free delivery
From our Sydney warehouse on every order
24/7 customer service
Contact us via phone, email, and live chat
Australia's #1
AU's biggest online contact lens, eyeglasses and sunglasses store
Learn more about joining the Clearly Australia family
Questions? We're here to help
Please get in touch with any queries or concerns. Our Vision Ambassadors are available 24/7 - call us at 1 800 639 478 or contact us online
Net Optical Australia is now part of Clearly Australia
We're excited to share that Net Optical Australia has merged with Clearly Australia, which means you can now shop for the contact lenses you already love, with plenty of new benefits.
Same awesome Aussie service - and so much more
Fast and free delivery
From our Sydney warehouse on every order
24/7 customer service
Contact us via phone, email, and live chat
Australia's #1
AU's biggest online contact lens, eyeglasses and sunglasses store
Learn more about joining the Clearly Australia family
Questions? We're here to help
Please get in touch with any queries or concerns. Our Vision Ambassadors are available 24/7 - call us at 1 800 639 478 or contact us online
WebContacts is now part of Clearly Australia
We're excited to share that WebContacts has merged with Clearly Australia, which means you can now shop for the contact lenses you already love, with plenty of new benefits.
Same awesome Aussie service - and so much more
Fast and free delivery
From our Sydney warehouse on every order
24/7 customer service
Contact us via phone, email, and live chat
Australia's #1
AU's biggest online contact lens, eyeglasses and sunglasses store
Learn more about joining the Clearly Australia family
Questions? We're here to help
Please get in touch with any queries or concerns. Our Vision Ambassadors are available 24/7 - call us at 1 800 639 478 or contact us online
YourContacts is now part of Clearly Australia
We're excited to share that YourContacts has merged with Clearly Australia, which means you can now shop for the contact lenses you already love, with plenty of new benefits.
Same awesome Aussie service - and so much more
Fast and free delivery
From our Sydney warehouse on every order
24/7 customer service
Contact us via phone, email, and live chat
Australia's #1
AU's biggest online contact lens, eyeglasses and sunglasses store
Learn more about joining the Clearly Australia family
Questions? We're here to help
Please get in touch with any queries or concerns. Our Vision Ambassadors are available 24/7 - call us at 1 800 639 478 or contact us online
